Repin Andrei

Full Stack developer (Python, JavaScript)

https://repin-andrei.com/

ABOUT MYSELF

I've been into programming since school, my first programming languages were Pascal, QBasic and then Delphi. Later at the institute, I programmed in C, C++ and PHP. After university, I started my career as a 1C developer. 1C software products were gaining popularity in Russia. After 6 years, I grew from a junior 1C developer to the head of a 1C development group. In parallel, I started learning other programming languages such as JavaScript and Python to expand my technology stack, so I got into Yandex-Practicum and completed two courses on front-end (JS) development and back-end (python) development for 10 months each. Already in the process of learning, it was possible to apply knowledge in commercial projects. The modern technology stack turned out to be more interesting and promising for me than 1C, and I decided to completely change the technology stack and become a full-stack developer.

PROJECTS

Service for money transfer to cards (commercial project) — API service (python + Django Rest Framework)

The application allows the internal accounting system or CRM system to interact with banks or fintechs and send money to suppliers' and clients' cards.

As a result of the service implementation, 1 out of every 4 customers receives card payments which allows to decrease the cash collection and transportation costs.

News Explorer (study project) (*JS + html/css + node.js + express.js + MongoDB*)

A project to search for news on various news portals using the API, the project also includes a personal account with the ability to save and delete your favorite news.

Mesto (study project) (JS + html/css + node.js + express.js + MongoDB) Mini social network with the ability to add photos, delete photos (only your own), leave likes for your favorite photos.

Telegram bot for monitoring system status (commercial project) (python).

As a result of the service implementation, fault tolerance has significantly increased and downtime has been reduced

Gruzolov (commercial project) — *Telegram bot (python)*

An application for river transporters search.

Talk-ed.com (commercial project) — Start-up at the initial stage (*ReactJS + HTML/CSS + python + Django*)

In collaboration with the Ural School of Negotiations, a portal uniting all schools of negotiations in Russia and abroad and helping to search for a duel opponent and a coach for review is being developed.

Goodlombard.ru (commercial project) — (My part is API service in JavaScript and also some promo pages) Web-site development for a chain of pawnshops incl. Web-site, Mobile app, API for interaction with the internal accounting system and external services. Currently, about 30% of customers use services developed for payments in their web-site accounts or in the mobile application which allowed to reduce staff load and avoid queues.

Trade (commercial project) — Development of software (accounting and analytics) for metal trade from scratch. (1C:Enterprise)

The company has been using the software for 7 years for operational analytical data receipt and decision making.

+7(922)223-66-43

Repin404@gmail.com

Telegram: @Repin404 Skype: repin404

Github: github.com/RA404

SKILLS

Python

Django

JavaScript

React

HTML / CSS

Django REST Framework

Express.js

PHP

Docker

Git

nginx

WebPack

CI/CD

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

Staffordhouse, London, UKIELTS Test Preparation

CES, Worthing, UK

Upper-Intermediate English Course

Ural School of Negotiations

Courses taken:

- Negotiations preparation
- Difficult negotiations
- Team negotiations
- Influence in negotiations
- Emotions in negotiations

Arena Multimedia

Web sites development PHP and MySQL

IT Academy

Internet advertising

Sergey Spivak training programme Internet advertising

LANGUAGES

Russian-Native

English-B2

WORK EXPERIENCE HOBBIES

April 2022-July 2022 - Preparation for admission to US universities

Program: MSc in Data Science

Chess

Snowboarding

January 2022-March 2022- "Talk-ed" Itd, Ekaterinburg, Teach Lead

Company profile: Educational project aimed at negotiations and managerial skills development based on the technology "Managerial duel" by K.V. Tarasov

Duties: MVP and IT architecture development, assembling the team of developers, code

review, product technical refinement and technical support.

August 2012-December 2021 - "Tekh-Met" Itd, Ekaterinburg, CTO (Mostly 1C:Enterprise)

Company profile: Transit of ferrous and non-ferrous scrap. Manufacturing sites. Procurement and processing of ferrous and non-ferrous scrap. Shipping company, transportation by river transport. Chain of pawnshops.

Duties: managing IT department with 5 employees, web-sites development for different products, organising a cooperation with sub-contractors

August 2006-May 2012 - Computer Programmer (1C:Enterprise)

Duties: New software development, updating of the existing software according to the customer's needs, technical tasks writing and completion.

"Kloss Services Corporation" Itd (June 2009-May 2012)

Company profile: Wholesale and retail trade of digital electronics

"AS-Deprix" ltd (January 2009-May 2009)

Company profile: Franchisee of "1C" (the most popular software product in Russia for business owners and accountants allowing to automate most of the business processes).

"Ural Electronic Plant" Itd (August 2006-December 2008)

Company profile: Manufacture of optical drives and flash cards, wholesale trade of "Mirex"

and "Laser Craft" trade marks.

EDUCATION

September 2006-June 2010

Ural State Technical University, Ekaterinburg (one of the biggest institutions of technical

higher education in Russia)

Department of Applied Computer Science in Economics

Bachelor (Specialist) Degree in Applied Computer Science in Economics

September 2003-June 2006

Ural Technological College, Sverdlovsk Region

Department of Software Engineering for Computers and Computer-based Systems Technician (Vocational qualification, diploma)

ADDITIONAL TRAINING

November 2020-October 2021

Python Backend Developer program, Yandex Practicum

I was a tech lead on a team project

September 2019-June 2020

Web Developer program, Yandex Practicum

After completing the course, I became a senior student to help other students learn web development

April 2012-April 2013

Higher School of Economics, Ekaterinburg

Professional training program "Mini MBA - Career (Management)"

September 2011-September 2012

Higher School of Economics, Ekaterinburg

Professional training program "Financial Management"